{
    "subject": "resource/Jim_Allen_(playwright)",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableWork",
    "object": "resource/The_Wednesday_Play",
    "human_readable": "Jim Allen is known for his notable work 'The Wednesday Play'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9105699062347412,
            "question": "What is the title of Jim Allen's notable work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8876327872276306,
            "question": "What is Jim Allen known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7947168946266174,
            "question": "Are there any other notable works by Jim Allen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5991005897521973,
            "question": "In what genre did Jim Allen make his notable contribution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4755779802799225,
            "question": "Who were some of the key collaborators on 'The Wednesday Play'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4176602363586426,
            "question": "What kind of impact did Jim Allen's work have on the industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3459711968898773,
            "question": "When was 'The Wednesday Play' produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3451918065547943,
            "question": "What are some of the themes explored in 'The Wednesday Play'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32483693957328796,
            "question": "Is 'The Wednesday Play' a book, film, or television series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30573078989982605,
            "question": "How has 'The Wednesday Play' been received by critics and audiences?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jim Allen is known for his notable work 'The Wednesday Play'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8181_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'The Wednesday Play' a book, film, or television series?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8181_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the themes explored in 'The Wednesday Play'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8181_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was 'The Wednesday Play' produced?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8181_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8181_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8181_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8181_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8181_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8181_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8181_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8181_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8181_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8181_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8181_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents mention Jim Allen's plays were part of \"The Wednesday Play\" series, it doesn't state that he's known for *that particular show* itself.  He is known for his plays and collaborations with Ken Loach. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\nIn one of the documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8181/re-ranker-msmarco/43.txt), it is mentioned that Jim Allen's first full-length play, \"The Hard Word\", was broadcast by the BBC in 1966 as part of their drama series \"The Wednesday Play\". Additionally, another document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8181/re-ranker-msmarco/81.txt) mentions that Jim Allen wrote plays such as \"THE LUMP\" and \"THE BIG FLAME\", which were part of the same series. Therefore, it can be inferred that Jim Allen is known for his notable work 'The Wednesday Play'."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The provided documents mention that Jim Allen was associated with \"The Wednesday Play\" series, including plays like \"The Hard Word\" and \"The Lump.\" This supports the statement that Jim Allen is known for his work on \"The Wednesday Play.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several texts state that Jim Allen wrote plays for \"The Wednesday Play\" which was a BBC drama series, not that he is known for the program itself.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}